express.com 2014-06-28

# Express | Shop Men's and Women's Clothing

### EXPRESS PRIVACY POLICY - YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS

Effective Date September 2011. (Last Updated October 2013)

  * THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES TO OUR SITES, STORES AND APPS.
  * WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM AND ABOUT YOU.
  * WE COLLECT INFORMATION IN DIFFERENT WAYS.
  * WE USE INFORMATION AS DISCLOSED AND DESCRIBED HERE.
  * WE MAY SHARE INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES.
  * YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT SHARING AND MARKETING PRACTICES.
  * YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.
  * THESE SITES AND CHILDREN.
  * WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES.
  * WE STORE INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS.
  * HOW YOU CAN ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION.
  * WE MAY LINK TO OTHER SITES OR HAVE THIRD PARTY SERVICES ON OUR SITE WE DON’T CONTROL.
  * FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE MORE QUESTIONS.
  * WE MAY UPDATE THIS POLICY.

### THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES TO OUR SITES, STORES AND APPS.

This Policy has been prepared by Express, LLC and Express Fashion Apparel Canada, Inc. (“we”). The Policy describes the manner in which we collect, use, disclosed and otherwise treat personal information at our stores, on our website, mobile sites and apps, and through other interactions with our customers.

### WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM AND ABOUT YOU.

#### We collect contact information.

For example, we might collect your name and street address if you register on our site. We might also collect your phone number or email address when you contact us with a request or question.

#### We collect payment information.

For example, we collect your credit or debit card number and related information if you make a purchase, and your name and signature when you return or exchange merchandise.

#### We collect information you submit or post.

We collect the information you choose to post in a public space on our site such as product reviews or comments on our blog. We also collect information when you contact us with a request or question.

#### We collect demographic information.

We may collect optional information like your gender and age. We may also collect your zip code/postal code. We might collect this when you contact us, sign-up for our mailing list or enter a contest or promotion.

#### We collect job-related information.

We may collect information you have provided in a resume or similar employment-related material.

#### We collect other information.

If you use our website, we may collect your IP address and information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it.

### WE COLLECT INFORMATION IN DIFFERENT WAYS.

#### We collect information directly from you.

For example, if you sign up for our mailing or email list or enter a contest or sweepstakes. We also collect information if you make a purchase, fill out an online survey or apply for a job. This includes information you provide us on our social networking sites.

#### We collect information from you passively.

We use tracking tools like browser cookies, pixel tags, web beacons and similar technologies. We also collect information from our mobile apps. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them, [here](http://www.express.com/aboutads). We may also use video surveillance in our stores.

#### We get information about you from third parties.

For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information associated with your social media account (such as your name, username, email address, profile picture, or gender).

#### We collect information about your friends and family.

For example, if you use the E-mail-a-Friend or other similar features on our site, we collect your name and email address as well as that of your friend or family member. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would be interested in receiving the message.If you purchase an E-GiftCard, we may collect the name and email address of the recipient. We do not use the names or email addresses submitted in these circumstances for any other purpose without consent.

### WE USE INFORMATION AS DISCLOSED AND DESCRIBED HERE.

#### We use information to provide you with the products or services you requested.

For example, we use information to process and administer your payments and deliver your online purchases or E-GiftCards. We also use information to administer your participation in our contests or sweepstakes.

#### We use information to respond to your requests or questions.

For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback and assist you in the future. We also use information you have provided in a resume or similar employment-related material to process and respond to your application for current and future career opportunities.

#### We use information to improve our sites, products and services.

We may use your information to make our website and products better and to better understand our customers. We might also use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties and publicly available sources, such as information to validate the accuracy of address or other information you have provided to us.

#### We use information for security purposes.

We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our sites and to administer our loss prevention program.

#### We use information for marketing purposes.

For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We might tell you about new features or updates. If you register with us, we may enroll you in our email newsletter. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps.

#### We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.

We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

#### We use information as otherwise disclosed to you, and as permitted or required by law.

### WE MAY SHARE INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES.

#### We may share information with our related entities.

For example, prior to 2010, this included The Limited, Victoria’s Secret, and Bath & Body Works.

#### We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.

For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our website or run a promotion for us. 

#### We may share information with our business partners.

For example, we may share information with third parties who co-sponsor a contest or promotion. These partners may send you information about events and products by mail or email.

#### We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.

For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests, or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable US or other law. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a sweepstakes or promotion. 

#### We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.

For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

#### We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

### YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT SHARING AND MARKETING PRACTICES.

#### You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.

To stop receiving our promotional emails, email us at [talk@express.com](mailto:talk@express.com) or follow the unsubscribe instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we may still send you transactional and administrative messages, such as responding to your questions or messages about your purchases.

#### You can opt out of receiving our text messages.

To stop receiving our text messages, text STOP to 397737. You can also opt out by emailing [talk@express.com](mailto:talk@express.com) and including your cell phone number or calling 1-800-477-8844.

#### You can control cookies and tracking tools.

To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, please click [here](http://www.express.com/aboutads).

#### You can control tools on your mobile devices.

For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. To modify the push notifications you get from our app, you can alter your preferences in your device settings.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please email [talk@express.com](mailto:talk@express.com) and include the title “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line.

### THESE SITES AND CHILDREN.

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at talk@express.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html). 

### WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES.

We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. However, the Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites or apps will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

### WE STORE INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to our affiliates or service providers in the United States or other jurisdictions, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

### HOW YOU CAN ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION.

You may have the right to access, update, and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updating and corrections by contacting us as set out below.

### WE MAY LINK TO OTHER SITES OR HAVE THIRD PARTY SERVICES ON OUR SITE WE DON’T CONTROL.

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of such websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party personal information or other practices.

Our site may also serve third party content that contains its own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies.

### FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE MORE QUESTIONS.

If you have any questions about this Policy or the manner in which we or our service providers treat your personal information, please email us at [talk@express.com](mailto:talk@express.com).

You can also write to us or call our **Privacy Officer** at: 

Express, LLC  
1 Express Drive  
Columbus, OH 43230  
Phone: 1-800-477-8844 

### WE MAY UPDATE THIS POLICY.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

© 2013 Express, LLC. All rights reserved.
